

CHAN JIE XU

Diploma in information technology.

018-781 1293

i23024517@student.newinti.edu.my

PROFILE

I'm Chan Jie Xu, a Diploma in IT student with experience in content creation, public relations, and digital marketing. As the Public Relations Officer for the 28th Student Action Club, I have honed my skills in event coordination, strategic communication, and editorial oversight. My ability to ensure clear, professional communication and manage publicity efforts.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Digital Marketing Content Creation Website Development Project Management Public Relation Team Collaboration Event Planning Problem Solving Adaptability

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jump Media Sdn Bhd Website Development Projects

May2024 - Aug2024

Designed the AISA website's front end using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, ensuring user-friendly navigation and alignment with brand messaging, which boosted site traffic and inquiries.

ALAIWA Thai Street 2024 Vice Organizing Chairperson

March2024 - Aug2024

Worked with sponsors Vida World Sdn. Bhd. and LANXY Group to secure funding, enhancing the event's scale. Managed a diverse team, ensuring effective communication for success.

SPECIAL EXPERIENCE

Participate in Public Exhibition

The 5th OCTF (Kuala Lumpur) Intelligent Technology Exhibition Franchise Expo Malaysia (FEM) 2024

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Diploma in Information Technology

June 2023 - current

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Public relationship officer, STACT Club Dec2023 - current

27th INTIMA Service Cell Jul2023 - Nov2023